[
	{
		"question": "**Whats my favorite color?**",
		"answers": ["yellow"]
	},
	{
		"question": "**What is the best drink?**",
		"answers": ["vodka", "mountain dew", "cum", "Vodka", "Mountain Dew", "Pussy Juice","blood","Blood"]
	},
    {
		"question": "**What am I watching?**",
		"answers": ["Eternally", "everything", "eternally", "Everything"]
	},
    {
		"question": "**What is my killstreak?**",
		"answers": ["1845","one thousand eight hundred forty-five","One thousand eight hundred forty-five"]
	},
    {
		"question": "**When do we ride?**",
		"answers": ["at dawn","At dawn","tonight with your mom","Before sunrise"]
	},
    {
		"question": "**What is my twitter name?**",
		"answers": ["@BigBird","BigBird","bigbird","@bigbird"]
	},
    {
		"question": "**How did Barrack Obama describe me?**",
		"answers": ["Evil Genius","evil genius","an evil genius","An Evil Genius"]
	},
    {
		"question": "**What do I have that other muppets don't have?**",
		"answers": ["A 12 inch penis","Golden Star on Hollywood walk of fame","big pp","Big Dick"]
	},
    {
		"question": "**What color is my Dutch friend?**",
		"answers": ["Blue","blue","light blue","Light Blue"]
	},
    {
		"question": "**What do I hate the most?**",
		"answers": ["Furry","Furries","Niggas","Niggers","Black People"]
    },
    {
		"question": "**Who runs my plantage?**",
		"answers": ["Slaves","slaves","Niggas","Niggers","Black People","niggers"]
    },
    {
		"question": "**When is my birthday?**",
		"answers": ["20 March","Twenty March","20 march","twenty march"]
    },
	{
		"question": "**What is my real name?**",
		"answers": ["Caroll Spinney","caroll spinney","Caroll spinney","caroll Spinney"]
    },
	{
		"question": "**What object is also named Big Bird?**",
		"answers": ["American spy satellite","KH-9 Hexagon","spy satellites","Spy Satellites","american spy satellites"]
    },
	{
		"question": "**Who is my favorite Muppet?**",
		"answers": ["me","Me","Elmo","elmo"]
    },
	{
		"question": "**How tall am I?**",
		"answers": ["249 cm","2 meter 49 cm","2 meter 49 cm","eight-foot two-inch","8\"2"]
    },
	{
		"question": "**On what channel can you see me?**",
		"answers": ["HBO","hbo","PBS","pbs","pbs kids","pbs-kids","PBS-Kids"]
    },
	{
		"question": "**What is the name of my chinese brother?**",
		"answers": ["Da Niao","da niao","nino","大鸟"]
    },
	{
		"question": "**Who made me?**",
		"answers": ["Aang","Aang#4033","DripDaddy","Jim Henson","jim henson"]
    },
	{
		"question": "**What does the letter \"U\" stand for?**",
		"answers": ["Unemployed","unemployed"]
    },
	{
		"question": "**What is the talles bird?**",
		"answers": ["Ostrich","ostrich","You bigbird","you master","You Master"]
    }

]